From Daily Wire published April
12th 2026 Liberal media wants
you to know they knew Eric
Swalwell was a sex pest and
didn't report a thing Liberal
media wants you to know they
knew Eric Swalwell was a sex
pest and didn't report a thing
Absolutely wild how the
Democratic Party cover for Eric
Swalwell for literally decades
because it suited their
political purposes April 12th
2026 dailywire com Listen to
this article John Lemparski
Getty Images A wave of sexual
assault accusations against Rep
Eric Swalwell DCA hit on Friday
In the time since a number in
the media and political spheres
have claimed that they knew all
along that the California
congressman was at best a pest
and at worst involved in
behavior that might be criminal
but never went public with that
information Local reporter
Stephen Taveras author of the
East Bay Insider said that he
had been covering Swalwell for
more than a decade beginning
when he was just a member of the
Dublin City Council and that he
and others had been well aware
of Swalwell's proclivities for
years I've covered Eric Swalwell
since he was a member of the
Dublin City Council Shortly
after being elected to Congress
in 2013 his behavior towards
women was known by all levels of
our local government and the
Alameda County Democratic Party
Taveras posted via X adding
Don't get it twisted Nobody has
been more critical of Swalwell
over the years I tried
repeatedly to get the stories
out I can't force women to speak
out and when they chose not to I
didn't push I also knew that
Swalwell was known to threaten
litigation But as critics
quickly pointed out knowing
information like that and not
reporting it could put young
women at risk Radio host Dana
Loesch summed it up and at no
time did you think gee maybe I
should report about this And it
wasn't just the local
journalists who said they'd long
had the dirt on Swalwell and
somehow none of them had gone
public with that information
either This Swalwell situation
was shall we say widely rumored
and it's interesting that the
gossip doesn't seem to have made
its way to all the big shots out
West Bloomberg columnist Matthew
Iglesias said Okay just to show
how insane this is I was
aggressively hit on two separate
times by Eric Swalwell one after
a DNC meeting at the hotel in
front of a ton of notable folks
and one in my DMs I don't think
he remembered me from the first
time when he hit me up in DMs
she posted on Saturday I showed
disinterest and like many others
heard stories which makes me
wonder why House leadership who
most certainly knew continued to
protect a member without looking
into it She continued and how
pathological of him to pressure
and allegedly essay subordinates
and think he was protected I
hope the NYAG's office
investigates thoroughly and it
sends a message to other people
in power who sexually abuse and
harass to stop and get out of
politics and for other survivors
to know they have a voice in
power But Const also did not say
anything until the story blew up
They've all known for years It's
been an open secret and I don't
say that as a guess Yashar Ali
confirmed Sean Van Diver
president of AfghaniVac took a
moment to apologize to everyone
he'd ever introduced to Swalwell
saying in an ex post The rumors
about him weren't new They had
been circulating for a long time
and many people were aware of
them When he asked for my
support in the California
gubernatorial race I raised
those concerns directly He
unequivocally denied them
dismissing it as Washington
rumor mill nonsense and claiming
there was no truth behind it He
framed it as behavior from when
he was single without
recognizing or acknowledging the
underlying power dynamics at
play I took him at his word That
was a mistake and a failure I
should have listened more
carefully to the people who
warned me I regret not taking
those concerns more seriously
and I regret the role I played
in lending him credibility We
all need to do better about who
we trust who we elevate and when
we choose to look the other way